Previously on "Friends"...
DON'T COME OUT HERE.
YOU CANNOT TELL CHANDLER,
BUT I RAN INTO RICHARD.
WHICH RICHARD?
MY EX-BOYFRIEND RICHARD.
THIS IS THE WORST THING
THAT CAN HAPPEN
ON AN ANNIVERSARY.
OH, GOOD. YOU DECIDED
TO TELL HIM
ABOUT THE
RICHARD THING.
OH, NO.
YOU CANNOT SEE HIM
EVER AGAIN.
YOU CAN'T TELL
ME WHAT TO DO.
THAT'S SO FUNNY.
I THINK
I JUST DID.
I HAVE FOUND
MY IDENTICAL HAND TWIN.
WHAT'S AN IDENTICAL
HAND TWIN?
IT'S A GUY WITH
MY IDENTICAL HANDS.
I'M GOING TO BE
A MILLIONAIRE.
YAY!
YES, COME ON!
YOU ACTUALLY THOUGHT
I WANTED TO HAVE SEX WITH YOU?
NO.
LAST NIGHT WAS EMBARRASSING
FOR YOU, TOO.
I JUST DON'T EMBARRASS
THAT EASILY.
I THINK THE CHECK-IN
IS THAT WAY.
AH.
( laughing )
( laughs )
HELLO!
OH, KIDS LOVE ME.
HEY!
PHOEBE!
YOU GUYS ARE HERE!
YAY!
WHAT'D YOU DO, GO
TO A COSTUME PARTY?
LET ME GUESS.
PANCHO VILLA.
( chuckling )
AND YOU'RE BOB SAGET.
"PANCHO VILLA"?
YEAH.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
PHEEBS? I DON'T...
( gasps )
OH, MY GOD!
YOU DREW ON ME?
HEY, YOU WET MY PANTS!
HEY...
WHOA, WHAT KIND
OF PARTY WAS THIS?
ROSS, I HAVE BEEN WALKING AROUND
LIKE THIS SINCE THE PLANE?
YOU HAVE SO CROSSED A LINE.
RACH, WAIT.
THE MEN'S ROOM IS THAT WAY.
( coins clinking )
OH!
WHAT?
THAT'S, LIKE, THE THIRD
TIME THAT LADY'S WON
ON A MACHINE
I WAS PLAYING.
OH, I BET SHE'S
ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE.
M-M-MOLE PEOPLE?
WHAT? NO. NO, A LURKER.
OH. WHAT'S A LURKER?
OKAY, WHEN YOU'RE
PLAYING A MACHINE
AND IT HASN'T PAID OUT
A LURKER WAITS FOR YOU
TO GIVE UP AND THEN...
KILLS YOU?
NO, THEY SWOOP IN
AND STEAL YOUR JACKPOT.
OH.
MM-HMM.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT THIS?
MY NANA USED
TO DO IT, MM-HMM.
THAT'S HOW SHE PAID
FOR ALL MY DANCE...
KARATE LESSONS.
DANCE KARATE?
YES. IT'S A DEADLY
BUT BEAUTIFUL SPORT.
OKAY
IT WON'T COME OFF.
WHAT?
OH, MY GOD.
RACH, ARE YOU SURE?
NO. ACTUALLY, I TOOK IT OFF
AND THEN I DREW IT BACK ON.
HEY, HEY!
YOU MADE IT!
JOEY! HEY, HEY!
HI.
WHO'S YOUR FRIEND?
HE'S HOT.
( chuckles )
THANKS, MAN.
HEY, LISTEN, I TALKED
TO CHANDLER.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THE MOVIE.
DON'T BE SORRY.
I DON'T NEED IT ANYMORE.
I FOUND MY IDENTICAL HAND TWIN.
YOUR WHAT?
MY IDENTICAL HAND TWIN.
YEAH, THE PERSON WHOSE HANDS
ARE EXACTLY LIKE MINE.
THIS THING
IS A GOLD MINE.
WHAT?
WHA...? HOW...?
THAT'S NOT GOING
TO MAKE YOU ANY MONEY.
OKAY. WELL, IF THAT'S
HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT IT, FINE.
NONE OF YOU ARE GOING
TO GET TO LIVE WITH ME
IN MY GREAT BIG
HAND-SHAPED MANSION.
'CEPT YOU, PHEEBS.
YOU CAN LIVE IN THE THUMB.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
ALL RIGHT, BABY, COME ON!
YES! YES!
YES!
I AM ON FIRE!
SEE YOU LATER, MON.
CHANDLER, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE?
I'M GOING HOME.
WAIT. WHY?
CHANDLER?
CHANDLER, LOOK.
I'M SORRY.
I WAS JUST PLAYING
FOR ONE SECOND.
I WAS TRYING TO FIND YOU
AND TELL YOU THAT...
LOOK, IF YOU DON'T WANT ME
TO SEE RICHARD AGAIN, I WON'T.
HE MEANS NOTHING TO ME.
OH, COME ON.
I WAS THERE.
I KNOW HE'S THE LOVE
OF YOUR LIFE.
NOT ANYMORE.
REALLY?
REALLY.
ALL RIGHT?
LET'S FORGET ABOUT THIS
"GOING HOME" STUFF
AND START CELEBRATING
OUR ANNIVERSARY.
OKAY, THIS IS EMPTY.
YEAH, I WANTED TO MAKE
A DRAMATIC SCENE
BUT I HATE PACKING.
( chuckles )
UH, HEY, WHERE'S
THE OTHER GUY?
WHICH GUY?
HE'S KIND OF TALL, DARK HAIR
HAND LOOKS
EXACTLY LIKE THIS, SEE?
I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THE HANDS
BUT THE GUY WHO WAS
HERE BEFORE ME
JUST WENT
TO THE RESTROOM.
OKAY.
HOW YOU DOING?
VERY BUSY.
ALL RIGHT! OKAY!
YES, HELLO, I
HAVE A QUESTION.
UM, I USED YOUR PEN TO
DRAW ON MY FRIEND'S FACE.
A BEARD AND A MUSTACHE.
( chuckles )
THANK YOU.
NO, SHE DIDN'T THINK SO.
I KNOW. IT'S, LIKE...
ANYWAY, UM...
MAKEUP DIDN'T COVER IT
AND WE'VE TRIED EVERYTHING
TO GET IT OFF
AND NOTHING'S WORKED.
WHAT DO WE DO?
YEAH.
UH-HUH... YEAH.
OH, OKAY.
OKAY, THANK YOU.
YEAH, IT'S NOT COMING OFF.
WHAT?
WHAT ELSE DID HE SAY?
UM, HE SAID HE THOUGHT
I WAS FUNNY, SO...
OKAY, LOOK, LOOK, LET'S JUST GO
DOWNSTAIRS, WE'LL HAVE SOME FUN
AND YOU WILL FORGET
ALL ABOUT IT.
ROSS, NO!
THERE IS NO WAY I AM LEAVING
THIS ROOM LOOKING LIKE THIS.
OH, COME ON, RACH,
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
ROSS, I AM
A HUMAN DOODLE!
LOOK, JUST BECAUSE
SOME IDIOT DREW
ON YOUR FACE
DOESN'T MEAN YOU
SHOULDN'T HAVE
ANY FUN, OKAY?
BESIDES-- HEY, HEY, HEY
NO ONE'S GOING TO EVEN
LOOK AT YOU, OKAY?
THIS IS VEGAS, HELLO?
THERE ARE TONS OF
OTHER FREAKS HERE.
FREAKS HERE, NO OTHER.
COME ON. NO ONE WILL
NOTICE, I SWEAR.
COME ON.
OKAY, THERE WAS
SOME STARING AND POINTING.
OKAY, I NEED, I NEED A DRINK.
HEY, YOU KNOW,
THEY REALLY OVERCHARGE YOU
FOR THAT STUFF.
BUT WHO CARES,
BECAUSE IT'S ALL ON ME.
( bottles clinking )
THAT IS ONE BIG DRINK.
MACADAMIA NUT?
UM, WOW!
THAT'S, THAT'S SOME PRICEY NUT.
MM.
YOU REALLY LIKE THOSE
MACADAMIA NUTS, HUH?
NOPE.
GET OUT OF HERE,
YOU LURKER!
GO ON, GET!
( coin clinks )
HEY, PHEEBS.
YOU MADE UP.
YEAH, I COULDN'T BE
MAD AT HIM FOR TOO LONG.
YEAH, SHE COULDN'T LIVE
WITHOUT THE CHAND-LOVE.
OKAY, GET A ROOM.
WE HAVE ONE.
I KNOW. USE IT.
OH, YEAH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU TAKE GOOD CARE
OF THOSE BABIES.
EXCUSE ME?
IT'S ME, JOEY.
DO I KNOW YOU?
JOEY...
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, THE HAND GUY.
OKAY, SO, WHAT ARE
WE GOING TO DO
ABOUT THIS HAND
TWIN THING?
NOTHING.
LOOK, YOU AND I HAVE
BEEN GIVEN A GIFT, OKAY?
WE HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING WITH IT
LIKE HAND MODELING, HUH?
OR MAGIC.
AND YOU KNOW NASA's GOING
TO WANT TO TALK TO US.
I HAVE TO GET
BACK TO WORK.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
WE COULD HAVE OUR
OWN SHOW, YOU KNOW?
WE COULD CLAP OUR
HANDS TOGETHER.
PEOPLE WILL LOVE IT
HUH?
AND I WROTE A SONG
FOR US.
♪ THIS HAND IS YOUR HAND ♪
♪ THIS HAND IS MY HAND ♪
♪ OH, WAIT, THAT'S YOUR HAND ♪
♪ NO, WAIT. IT'S MY HAND. ♪
SEE?
THAT'S OKAY.
BUT YOU HAVEN'T EVEN
HEARD THE CHORUS!
OH, MY GOD.
I'M STARTING TO LOOK
LIKE MY GREAT-AUNT MURIEL.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE DON'T HAVE TO GO DOWNSTAIRS.
WE CAN BRING VEGAS UP TO US.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON. COME ON.
LET'S GO. WE'LL PLAY
SOME BLACKJACK.
HERE WE GO. 13.
HIT ME.
OOH, 23.
WHICH IS WHAT WE PLAY TO
AT THIS CASINO.
YOU WIN TEN DOLLARS.
I BET $20.
RIGHT.
( people clamoring )
A NEW PAIR OF SHOES
FOR THE CHAN-CHAN MAN.
YES!
I'VE NEVER SEEN A ROLL
LIKE THIS IN MY LIFE!
THAT'S RIGHT, BABY!
OKAY, WHAT DO
I WANT NOW?
OKAY, UH, AN EIGHT.
UH, A SIX.
PICK A NUMBER!
THAT IS YOUR ONLY JOB!
EIGHT, EIGHT.
THANK YOU.
OKAY, IF YOU
GET THIS ONE
WE BUY EVERYBODY
HERE A STEAK DINNER.
( all cheer )
Croupier:
EIGHT AGAIN.
YES! YES!
WE AREN'T REALLY GOING
TO BUY THESE PEOPLE
STEAK DINNERS, ARE WE?
NO.
OKAY, GOOD.
OKAY, WHAT DO I WANT NOW?
UH, TRY A HARD EIGHT.
WHAT?
TWO FOURS.
OKAY.
Croupier:
EIGHT THE HARD WAY.
YES!
DON'T YOU LET HER GO.
YOU'RE A LUCKY GUY.
THANK YOU,
MR. DRUNKEN GAMBLER.
OKAY, YOU GET THIS
AND WE GET THE BIGGEST
SUITE IN THE PLACE.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
WE GET THE BIGGEST
SUITE IN THE PLACE.
( all groan )
ALL RIGHT, THE BIGGEST SUITE
IN THE PLACE.
COME ON.
YES! I LOVE YOU!
I CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER
WHAT WE WERE FIGHTING ABOUT.
THAT'S 'CAUSE I HAD
LUNCH WITH RI...
ME, NEITHER!
OKAY, WHAT DO I WANT NOW?
ANOTHER HARD EIGHT.
"HARD EIGHT"?
YOU SHOULD CALL IT
"EASY EIGHT."
OKAY, OKAY,
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU ROLL ANOTHER
HARD EIGHT...
AND WE GET MARRIED
HERE TONIGHT.
COME ON, ROLL!
SHUT UP!
IT JUST GOT INTERESTING!
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
YOU ROLL ANOTHER
HARD EIGHT
AND WE GET MARRIED
HERE TONIGHT.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YES. I LOVE YOU.
I'VE NEVER LOVED ANYBODY
AS MUCH AS I LOVE YOU.
OKAY, SO IF AN
EIGHT COMES UP
WE TAKE IT AS A SIGN
AND WE DO IT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
OKAY!
OKAY.
HARD EIGHT.
( everyone cheering )
( disappointed groans )
OKAY, THAT'S A FOUR!
AND WHERE... WHERE...
WHERE'S THE OTHER ONE?
IT WENT UNDER THE TABLE.
NOBODY MOVE!
OKAY, YOU LOOK THAT WAY,
I'LL LOOK THIS WAY!
HERE IT IS.
THAT COULD BE
A FOUR OR A FIVE.
IT'S YOUR CALL.
IT'S A FOUR.
I THINK SO, TOO.
OH, WELL. LOST AGAIN.
THAT'S IT!
YOU AND ME, OUTSIDE!
I WOULDN'T WANT
TO SEE YOU LOSE
A CHUNK OF THAT
PRETTY BLOND HAIR.
OH!
BE COOL. BE COOL.
( quietly conversing )
OKAY, LADY, YOUR LURKING DAYS
ARE OVER.
WHAT?!
YEAH.
FROM NOW ON, EVERYONE YOU LURK
I'M GOING TO LURK FIRST.
IF YOU MOVE ON TO SOMEONE ELSE
I'M GOING TO BE
ONE STEP AHEAD OF YOU
EVERY SINGLE TIME.
AND THEN I'LL BE ON YOUR ASS
EVERY HOUR OF EVERY DAY...
TILL MONDAY.
'CAUSE THAT'S WHEN I GO HOME.
WHEN DO YOU LEAVE?
ALSO MONDAY.
WHAT TIME?
MAYBE WE CAN SHARE A CAB.
HIT ME.
( heavy sigh )
WE NEED MORE CARDS.
YEAH, AND WE ALSO NEED
MORE, UM, DRINKS.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
WOOP. OKAY.
HELLO, VEGAS? YEAH.
WE WOULD LIKE SOME MORE ALCOHOL
AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
WE WOULD LIKE SOME MORE BEERS.
WHA...? HELLO?
OH, I FORGOT TO DIAL.
( knocking on door )
THAT MUST BE OUR ALCOHOL
AND BEERS.
HEY.
HEY, IT'S JOEY!
I LOVE JOEY!
Rachel:
OH, I LOVE JOEY!
OH, JOEY LIVES WITH A DUCK.
HI!
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, LOOK,
LOOK, YOU GUYS.
I NEED SOME HELP, OKAY?
SOMEONE HAS GOT
TO HELP ME
CONVINCE MY HAND TWIN
TO COOPERATE.
I'LL DO IT.
HEY, WHATEVER YOU NEED
ME TO DO, I'M YOUR MAN.
HEY.
WHOA... WHOA... WHOA.
ARE YOU... ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH. FINE. THANKS.
HEY, RACH.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
I'M DOIN' GOOD, BABY.
YEAH.
ROSS, DON'T LET HER DRINK
ANYMORE.
OH...
HERE'S THAT MACADAMIA NUT.
OH.
NOPE. SOMETHING ELSE.
OOPS.
( Rachel laughing )
ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO DO NOW?
I WANT TO GET OUT OF
THE ROOM.
I... YOU KNOW, I...
I REALLY MISS DOWNSTAIRS.
MMM.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE IS ONLY ONE WAY I AM
LEAVING THIS HOTEL ROOM.
WELL, HELLO.
HI. WELCOME TO VEGAS.
I'M ROSS.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
YOU'VE GOT A LITTLE
SOMETHING RIGHT...
( both laughing )
OH.
WOW.
HELLO.
( meowing ):
NO! OH!
WHOO!
I WON!
I WON! I FINALLY WON!
I WON! THAT WAS MY QUARTER!
HERE. TAKE A HIKE, TOOTS.
( gasping )
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
THIS LADY PLAYED
MY QUARTER.
THIS IS MY MONEY.
IS THAT TRUE, MISS?
( mumbling ):
UM... SELLS DRUGS TO KIDS.
WHAT?
SHE SELLS DRUGS TO KIDS.
IT WAS MY QUARTER.
WAS IT HER QUARTER?
HOW ABOUT WE TALK ABOUT THIS
OVER DINNER, HUH?
OKAY, LADY, YOU'RE
OUT OF HERE.
NO, NO, YOU
CAN'T ARREST ME!
NO, I WON'T GO BACK!
I WON'T GO BACK TO
THAT HELLHOLE!
I'M JUST TAKING YOU OUTSIDE.
OH, OKAY.
Monica:
OKAY, COME ON, I
CAN'T GET MARRIED
UNTIL I GET SOMETHING
OLD, SOMETHING NEW
SOMETHING BORROWED
AND SOMETHING BLUE.
OKAY, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
OKAY, HERE'S SOMETHING
BLUE AND NEW.
YOU ARE SO EFFICIENT.
I LOVE YOU.
LET'S GO.
NO, NO, NO, WAIT!
WE NEED SOMETHING OLD.
UH, OKAY... I HAVE A
CONDOM IN MY WALLET
THAT I'VE HAD
SINCE I WAS 12.
THAT'LL WORK.
I DON'T THINK SO.
OKAY, NOW WE JUST NEED
SOMETHING BORROWED.
HERE, JUST TAKE THIS.
THAT'S STEALING.
WE'LL... WE'LL BRING IT BACK.
JUST PUT IT UNDER YOUR DRESS.
AW.
OKAY, ONE THING AT A TIME.
( groaning )
ARE YOU GOING TO PLAY?
NO, NO. I DON'T REALLY
HAVE ANY MONEY.
( chuckling )
NOT YET, ANYWAY. HUH?
CAN'T SIT HERE IF YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO PLAY.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, YEAH.
OH, HOO-HOO-HOO-HOO.
OH...
HELLO.
MY NAME IS REGINA FILANGIE.
I'M A BUSINESSWOMAN
IN TOWN ON BUSINESS.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE MY CARD?
OH, WHAT DID I DO
WITH MY FILOFAX?
I MUST'VE LEFT IT IN
CONFERENCE ROOM "B."
FOURTEEN.
HIT ME.
OH, MY GOD.
MAY I JUST SAY THAT
YOU TWO GENTLEMEN
HAVE THE EXACT SAME HANDS?
( Joey gasping )
THEY'RE IDENTICAL.
NOW, I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE THAT IN THE BUSINESS WORLD.
STOP IT.
MISS FILANGIE?
MAY I ASK YOU A QUESTION
AS AN IMPARTIAL PERSON
AT THIS TABLE?
PLEASE STOP IT.
HUH... UH, WOULDN'T
YOU PAY GOOD MONEY
TO SEE THESE IDENTICAL
HANDS SHOWCASED
IN SOME TYPE OF A, UH,
ENTERTAINMENT VENUE, HUH?
IF YOU LEAVE NOW, I WILL CHOP
OFF MY HAND AND GIVE IT TO YOU.
DIDN'T I JUST THROW
YOU OUT OF HERE?
NO, YOU THREW OUT PHOEBE.
I'M REGINA FILANGIE.
FILANGIE.
COME ON, LADY.
PLEASE... PLEASE TAKE HIM, TOO.
ME?! OH, COME ON, MAN.
FORGET ABOUT IT,
BUDDY. COME ON.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
DON'T LET HIM DO THIS! COME ON!
I'M YOUR HAND TWIN!
HELLO. ONE MARRIAGE, PLEASE.
YEP. WE WANT
TO GET MARRIED.
WELL, THERE'S A
SERVICE IN PROGRESS.
HAVE A SEAT.
ALL RIGHT.
( humming "Pomp and
Circumstance" )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
UH, THAT'S
"THE WEDDING MARCH."
DOES THAT FREAK YOU OUT?
NO, ONLY BECAUSE IT'S
THE GRADUATION SONG.
( wedding processional playing)
OKAY, THIS IS IT.
WE'RE GOING TO GET MARRIED.
ARE YOU SURE YOU
WANT TO DO THIS?
( both laughing )
WELL, HELLO, MRS. ROSS.
WOO-HOO! WELL,
HELLO, MR. RACHEL.
( both laughing )
WAIT! OKAY.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]